(Amy:)I don't think any of us would be
sitting in this room right now.
(Howard:)Really? Sheldon not being here
(Howard:)is the main reason I'm in this room.
(Amy:)It's true.
(Amy:)None of you would know me.
(Amy:)You wouldn't know Bernadette.
(Amy:)-You wouldn't be dating Penny.
-You don't know that.
(Leonard:)I've been going to the
Cheesecake Factory for years.
(Leonard:)I could have picked her up.
(Penny:)Oh, you weren't joking.
(Leonard:)No.
(Penny:)Okay, sweetie, let me tell you
(Penny:)exactly how that
would have gone down.
(Leonard:)I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna ask her out.
(Howard:)I'm gonna squirt chocolate milk
out of my nipples.
(Howard:)Sorry, I thought we're saying things
that are never gonna happen.
(Raj:)Maybe this time
he's going to do it.
(Howard:)Hope you're thirsty, here it comes.
(Leonard:)Watch me.
(Penny:)Hey, you guys ready to order
or you need a few minutes?
(Penny:)-A few minutes it is.